Guide to the Women's Refugee Commission Records, 1979-2020; 1979-ongoing, bulk 1989-2011 RL.01405
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Washington, D.C. Office Files Series, 1992-2006, 6 boxes
  - Files relating to Haiti
    - Haiti-United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) Press Release, 2006 (Box 47)
    - Miami, 2006 Jan. 31-Feb. 3 (Box 47)
    - Domestic Delegation: New Orleans Background (Box 47)
    - Domestic Delegation: New Orleans (Box 47)
    - New Orleans Report Follow-up (Box 47)
    - Future of Democracy and Development in Haiti Symposium, 2005 Jul. 22-24 (Box 47)
  - Other D.C. Office Files
    - Advocacy Day, 1999 (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Day, 2000 (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Day, 2000 (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Day, 2001 (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Day, 2004 (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Day, 2005 Mar. (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Day, 2005 Board Meeting (Box 47)
    - Advocacy (Box 47)
    - Advocacy Statements (Box 47)
    - Roundtable Background Material: US/Canada/Australia Guidelines Comparisons (Box 47)
    - Unlabeled notebook (Box 47)
    - EMD (Box 47)
    - AILA v. Janet Reno, 1999 (Box 47)
    - Women's Commission Board Standing Committees (Box 47)
    - Women's Commission: Youth Speaks Out (Box 47)
    - Women's Commission: Board Meeting, 2004 Feb. 25 (Box 47)
    - Handouts/Materials (Box 47)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 47)
    - Steering Committee (Box 47)
    - Roundtable: Participants and Invitations (Box 48)
    - Roundtable: Follow-up (Box 48)
    - Press Conference Speakers (Box 48)
    - Roundtable Background Material: FGM (Box 48)
    - Roundtable Background Material: General/Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Roundtable Background Material: Convention Against Torture (Box 48)
    - Piedmont (Box 48)
    - Take Action/Leg for Web (Box 48)
    - International Pin Bill (Box 48)
    - Tripartite Consultations on Resettlement, Geneva, 2000 Jul. 3-4 (Box 48)
    - Ethnic and Religious Conflict Seminar, 2004 Oct. 1-3 (Box 48)
    - Women's Commission Board Meeting, 2007 Mar. 20 (Box 48)
    - ASKA (Box 48)
- New York Office Files Series
  The New York Office Files Series includes material related to the rebranding of the Commission's logo and general design issues, planning anniversary celebrations, launches for reports and book publications, and general files on communications and accountability working groups.
  Boxes 60-61 of this series are from Accession 2016-0110.
  - Design/Rebranding, 2008-2009 and undated (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Tagline, 2009 (Box 60)
  - Branding Materials, 2008-2009 (Box 60)
  - Branding--Legal, 2010 (Box 60)
  - Branding Development, undated (Box 60)
  - Legal, 2008 (Box 60)
  - Rebranding, 2008 (Box 60)
  - 25th Anniversary, 2013-2014 and undated (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - 25 Anniv. Campaign Stories, 2013-2014 (Box 61)
  - 20th Anniversary, 2007-2008 (Box 61)
  - Poems for Life, 1994-1995 (Box 61)
  - BOD Advoc. & Comm. Committee, 1992-2007 (Box 61)
  - Landmines Awareness Tour--Media, 5/1996 (Box 61)
  - Communications Audit, [2007] (Box 61)
  - Launch of First-Ever Guidance on Safe Access to Cooking Fuel...., 2009 (Box 61)
  - Launch of "Disabilities among Refugee and Conflict-Affected Populations", 2008 (Box 61)
  - Meetings, 1990-1997 (3 folders) (Box 61)
  - Accountability Working Group, 2007-2010 and undated (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Acc. Working Group, 2010 (Box 61)
  - Design Brochure (Susan Cook), 2009 (Box 61)
  - Design -- Seth, 06/2009 (Box 61)
  - Strategic Planning, 2006 (Box 61)
  - Sierra Leone: Children's Drawings, undated (Box 61)